Darko Djokic

Senior 3D Website & WebGL & Game & Full Stack Engineer

sislight0224@gmail.com

+12394448160

Texas, United State

live:.cid.3414237e4a0428af

https://portfolio-zeta-five-82.vercel.app/#home

Profile

Experienced Game Developer | Graphics Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the Game Development industry and field of 2D/3D Rendering. Skilled in Unity3D, WebGL, Casual Games, Gameplay Programming, Multiplayer, PC, Console, Web, and Mobile Games. I have worked on world-class projects in India as well as in Malaysia, China, Singapore, UK, USA on-site. And freelance for worldwide clients.

GAME ENGINES

- Unity3D, Unreal Engine, GameMaker

WEB GAME ENGINES

- HTML5 Canvas, WebGL, ThreeJS, BabylonJS, PlayCanvas, Construct3, PixiJS, ImpactJS, Phaser.IO 🗷 **GAME DESIGNS**
- Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Flash, 3D Max, Maya, Spine, ZBrush
- SmartFox Server, Photon Server, UNet, Player.IO ☑, Node.JS, WebSockets, Socket.IO ☑, MySQL, PHP, AWS, .NET

PLATFORMS

- PC, Mac, Consoles, iOS, Android, Windows UWP, Windows Phone, WebGL, Google Cardboard, Steam, Daydream, Facebook Gameroom

Professional Experience

Trotessional Experience	
2024/03 - 2024/10	3D Graphic Software Engineer
Seattle, USA	Oleg Maslov
	I developed rendering techniques, shader programming, and optimizing performance in real-time environments.
	This project is 3d idle unity game project. Game server, multiplayer logic, Inventory &
	Merchant system
2021/12 - 2024/02	Senior Software Engineer Team Lead
	Excellarate
	Creating and Implementing stunning WebGL Graphics Visualization for one of the
	world's largest providers of products and services to the energy industry.
	skill: Unreal Engine, Unity, WebGL, javascript, python, Blueprint
2020/07 - 2021/06	Senior WebGL Developer
	Verdiseno, Inc
	This role involves implementing new capabilities to the front end of a WebGL-based
	graphical design tool and increasing test coverage using Three.js, React.js, Mobx, and
	Storybook. Lyra Solar and Solar Design Tool.

2020/01 - 2021/01**Unity Game Developer**

Terahard Ltd

Worked on a world class upcoming fighter game in Unity3D using DOTS and ECS Jobs

https://store.steampowered.com/app/417130/Era/

2019/07 - 2019/12

Graphics Engineer

Homevista Decor and Furnishings Pvt. Ltd

Worked on a 3D virtual interior design platform for the browser using WebGL and ThreeJS. http://spacecraft.homelane.com

2018/05 - 2019/04

WebGL Developer

Inmagine Innovation Sdn. Bhd

Worked on world class image editing WebGL Projects and

WebGL Games http://www.pixlr.com/x/ | http://www.pixlr.com/e/

2017/03 - 2018/07

Frontend Developer

Beats by Dre

Contributed to fully rebuild the front-end with React and Redux.

Fashioned CSS to exactingly style to match received artwork and keep interactive and responsive style.

Replied with near immediate updates to requested changes from the Dr. Dre project manager.

-HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React, Redux

2014/07 - 2017/04

Game Developer

Logic Simplified

Game Development in Unreal Engine, Unity3D, ImpactJS, JavaScript-WebGL, Node.JS, Socket.IO for Multiple Mobile and Desktop Devices. The job responsibility in this company includes development of 2D and 3D games in Unity3D-C#, Unreal-C++ after the assets are provided by the design team. I have also developed games for web browsers here using Three.JS, ImpactJS and Phaser libraries.

Skills

Programming Languages/Frameworks ● ● ● ●

Blueprint, Python, C#, Go, Ruby, C/C++, JavaScript, Java, Swift, kotlin, TypeScript, Java, Ruby, React, Next.js, Vue, Angular, Express, Django, Flask, FastAPI, Three.js, WebGL, Web3, HTML 5, Html, CSS.

AI Techniques

Natural Language Processing, Machine Learning, Computer Vision, Data Science, Deep Learning, Image Processing, LLMs, Langchain, Pinecone, ChatGPT, OpenAI, Chatbot, TTS, STT

Backend Tech



- Mentoring & Training for Developers
- Automated Testing & CI/CD
- Distributed Caching Systems
- Data Storage Solutions
- Automated Deployment Pipeline
- Payment Gateways
- Monitoring & Alerting Systems
- Cloud Migration & Infrastructure
- Container Management
- IaaS & PaaS

Cloud Computing

AWS, GCP, Axure, Sagemaker

Education

2014/09 - 2018/04

Master's Degree

University of Fukui Japan Information Technology